cashflowfunnel.com 2019-05-22

# DailyPaySecret.com Privacy Policy

**What kind of personal information DailyPaySecret.com collects and how it is collected** ::

The **CashFlowFunnel.com** **Network (heretofore referred to simply as** CashFlowFunnel.com **)** **** collects personal information from prospective members via a 100% voluntary double opt-in lists and and voluntary submission of information of members or prospective members. 

In general, the personal information **CashFlowFunnel.com** collects includes (but is not limited to) name, address, contact details,  in some cases membership of professional associations. **CashFlowFunnel.com** does not collect or store financial information, including credit card information, banking details or income information. 

**  *CashFlowFunnel.com _DOES NOT_ sell, rent, or trade any information collected _under any circumstances._**

**Use of DailyPaySecret.com   is intended for individuals above the age of 18 ONLY.**

_Personal Information you provide_ : We store the personal information you enter on the **DailyPaySecret.com** Network. We obtain most personal information through the cash2flow.com  membership registration process and updates to membership details. You may provide information when you request or acquire a product or service from CashFlowFunnel.com or its related companies,, complete a survey or questionnaire, enter a competition, participate in forums or when you communicate with CashFlowFunnel.com by e-mail, telephone or in writing (for example if you contact customer service or provide feedback). You may "opt out" of any further communications with CashFlowFunnel.com if you so desire. 

_Automatic collection_ : Cookies: We may use a feature of your browser called a cookie to assign your computer a 'User ID'. Cookies **DO NOT** contain information by which CashFlowFunnel.com can identify you personally. They identify your computer to our servers. **You may configure your browser so that you are notified before a cookie is downloaded or so that your browser does not accept cookies.** CashFlowFunnel.com may use information contained in cookies to make assumptions about the user of the computer and to provide users of that computer with focused advertising which **CashFlowFunnel.com** believes may be of interest, based on that information. To disable your cookies, please refer to the help menu within your Internet browser. CashFlowFunnel.com DOES NOT track you on the internet in any way, shape, or form other then on our servers. **CashFlowFunnel.com DOES NOT track your surfing habits, purchases, demographics, searches, or ANY activity you engage in online other than what directly relates to our website on our servers.**

_Indirect collection_ : CashFlowFunnel.com endeavors to collect personal information about an individual **only from that individual.** In some circumstances CashFlowFunnel.com may obtain personal information from a third party. If you provide personal information about another person to CashFlowFunnel.com , CashFlowFunnel.com requires that you inform that person you have done so and provide them with a copy of this policy. 

**How CashFlowFunnel.com uses the information you provide**  
CashFlowFunnel.com may use information it collects from you for the primary purpose for which it is collected and for such other secondary purposes that are related to the primary purpose of collection. 

CashFlowFunnel.com generally uses personal information to: 

  * provide you with products or services you have requested 
  * personalize and customize your experiences on the CashFlowFunnel.com Network; 
  * help CashFlowFunnel.com manage and enhance its services; 
  * communicate with you; 
  * provide you with ongoing information about opportunities on the **CashFlowFunnel.com** Network in which CashFlowFunnel.com believes you may be interested; 
  * give you the opportunity from time to time to receive e-mail and 'e-newsletters' from **CashFlowFunnel.com.**

In most cases where CashFlowFunnel.com asks you to provide information about yourself, if you do not provide CashFlowFunnel.com with that information, **CashFlowFunnel.com** will not be able to provide you with the requested product or service. 

**CashFlowFunnel.com** may also provide your information to: 

  * third parties engaged by **CashFlowFunnel.com** to perform functions on its behalf, such as processing credit card information, mail outs, debt collection, marketing, research and advertising; 

If CashFlowFunnel.com sells part of its business, personal information may be part of the assets transferred to the purchaser. 

The CashFlowFunnel.com Network contains features where you are invited to send personal information to organizations other than CashFlowFunnel.com. The choice to send such information to these organizations is entirely yours. You should be aware that any such information you choose to send will not be bound by this policy CashFlowFunnel.com is NOT responsible for the Privacy Policies of other websites or blogs.

**How DCashFlowFunnel.com treats sensitive information**

**"Sensitive Information"** means information relating to a person's racial or ethnic origin, membership of political bodies, religion, membership of a trade union or professional or trade association, sexual preferences, criminal record , health (none of which we don't collect anyway). . 

CashFlowFunnel.com may use and disclose Sensitive Information only for the purpose for which it was provided or a directly related secondary purpose or as allowed by law unless you have agreed otherwise. 

**Management and security of personal information**  
CashFlowFunnel.com has appointed a Privacy Officer to oversee CashFlowFunnel.com 's management of personal information in accordance with this policy and the Commonwealth Privacy Act. 

CashFlowFunnel.com protects the personal information CashFlowFunnel.com holds from misuse, loss, unauthorized access, modification or disclosure by various means including firewalls, pass word access, secure servers and encryption of credit card transactions. 

**Updating personal information**  
CashFlowFunnel.com endeavors to ensure that the personal information it holds is accurate, complete and up-to-date. You can update your DailyPaySecret.com membership information via the 'Update your details' section on any of the sites within the CashFlowFunnel.com. 

**Seeking access to the personal information CashFlowFunnel.com holds about you**  
You have the right to seek access the personal information held about you and to advise CashFlowFunnel.com of any inaccuracy. There are some exceptions to this right set out in the Privacy Act. 

If you make an access request, DailyPaySecret.com will ask you to verify your identity and specify what information you require. CashFlowFunnel.com may charge a fee to cover the costs of meeting your request. 

_Membership information:_ CashFlowFunnel.com Network Members can access the membership information CashFlowFunnel.com holds about them at any time via the 'Update your details' section on any of the sites within the CashFlowFunnel.com Network. 

**How to contact CashFlowFunnel.com**  
If you have inquiries or wish to provide feedback about this policy, please e-mail [support@cashflowfunnel.com](mailto:Support@CashFlowFunnel.com). 

Close Window
